Guide to the Chit Chat Club Records, 1877-2010 M0158
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series II. Essays
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 'From Whence Cometh My Help?' Psalm 121, typescript, Harold C. Bradley, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Medical Manpower in our Changing Times, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - The Ties that Bind, typescript, W.B. Kuder, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Rings, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Jack London – Man Overboard, manuscript, Henry K. Evers, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Sterling, typescript, Chauncey D. Leake, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - The Parameters of Education, typescript, John B. Condliffe, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Activism, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - The Price, typescript, Ira B. Joralemon, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 1: Into the World, typescript, George Stewart, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Traveling behind the Iron Curtain, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Locus Sigilli,, typescript Frank H. Sloss, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Chit Chat Club: The First Quarter Century, typescript, William Kuder, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - The Predicament of Mankind, typescript, Frederic C. Searles, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Constitutional Crisis – Do We Have One? typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - To Melt Or Not To Melt - That's Not The Question, typescript, Dean C. Julian Bartlett, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - The Mars Experience, typescript, Donald C. Shane, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Four-Letter Words, typescript, George Stewart, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - The Barking Dog, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Forgotten Men, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Defunct Economists, typescript, John B. Condliffe, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - On Essays, typescript, William Kuder, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Decisions, Decisions, typescript, Frederick T. Searles, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - The Bear Flag Revolt, manuscript, Henry X. Evers, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Centennial Chit-Chat, typescript, William Kuder, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Chit Chat Club Centennial Dinner, November 11, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Seven Years, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - An Irreverent Reverend, typescript, Chauncey D. Leake, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Escape! typescript, G. Vansina, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Lean and Flashy Songs, typescript, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - The Pursuit of Aphrodite, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - The Dowager Queen, typescript, James R. Browning, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Steller, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Not With My Crowd You Don’t! typescript, Joseph T. Sneed, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz, typescript, Howard R. Williams, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Pirates, Priests, Presidents and Professors, typescript, Albert Jonsen, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Sauce for the Gander, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Progress, typescript, John Saunders, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - A Wandering Vine, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - International Training of Singers, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Abortion, typescript, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - A Piece of Paper, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 7)
    - A Hogshead of Sense? typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The Problem of Equality: Serrano versus Board of Education in 1954, typescript, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Not Good Behavior, typescript, Joseph T. Sneed, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Remember the Hummingbird…and Other Fables, typescript, Willard Hamilton, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - The Medicine–man, the Law-man and the Clergy-man, typescript, Howard R. Williams, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - Polo Anyone? typescript, Henry K. Evers, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 5)
    - Exploration, typescript, Charles Renfrew, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 6)
    - The Exhausting Life of the First Duke of Castries, typescript, Murray Richards, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Gods, Heroes and Monsters, typescript, William B. Kuder, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Back to the Ocean, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Who is Crippling Whom? typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - The Red Blanket, typescript, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - In Solemn Silence, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - Somewhere West of Laramie, typescript, Julian Bartlett, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Heredity and Environment, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Exploring the Cosmos with Lewis and Clarke, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - The Best Offense, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Shepherds, Loaves and Fishes, typescript, Willard F. Hamilton, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Salt, typescript, Howard H. Williams, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - The Quest for the Spice of Life, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - The Bible: Fact or Fiction? typescript, William B. Kuder, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Lights in the Dark, typescript, Joseph T. Sneed, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Activism, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - The Parameters of Education, typescript, John B. Condliffe, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - The Price, typescript, Ira B. Joralemon, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Into the World, typescript, George R. Stewart, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Travelling Behind the Iron Curtain, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Locus Sigilli, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Chit Chat Club - The First Quarter Century, typescript, William Kuder, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - The Predicament of Mankind, typescript, Frederick T. Searls, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Francisco Solano, typescript, Henry K. Evers, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Constitutional Crisis - Do We Have One? typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - To Melt Or Not to Melt - That's Not The Question, typescript, Dean C. Julian Bartlett, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - The Mars Experience, typescript, C. Donald Shane, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays and miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - To The Ladies (poem), typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Welcome To The Ladies (poem), typescript, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Centennial Dinner: Chit Chat Club, San Francisco (menu), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - The Bear Flag Revolt, manuscript (photocopy), Henry K. Evers, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - The Barking Dog, typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - The Four-letter Words, typescript, Stewart, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 6)
    - Forgotten Men, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 7)
    - Defunct Economists, typescript, John B. Condliffe, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 8)
    - On Essays, typescript, William Kuder, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Decisions, Decisions, typescript, Frederick T. Searls, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 10)
    - Chit-Chat Club Centennial Chit-Chat, typescript, William B. Kuder, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 11)
    - Seven Years, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 12)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lean and Flashy Songs, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - An Irreverent Reverend: Charles Lutwidge Dodgson, or Lewis Carroll, 1832-1898, typescript, Chauncey D. Leake, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Sauce for the Gander, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - A Wandering Vine, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - A Hogshead of Sense? typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Remember the Hummingbird...and Other Fables, typescript, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Who is Crippling Whom? typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - In Solemn Silence, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Somewhere West of Laramie..., typescript, Julian Bartlett, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - The Best Offense, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Goethe's Final Words, typescript, John E. McCosker, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - A More Fatal Disease than Cholera, Typhoid Fever and the Rest Put Together, typescript, Charles B. Renfrew, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - A Greed for History, typescript, William Robert Reilly, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Einthoven, Enthoven and Entitlement, typescript, R. Prescott, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - The Barker's Children, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12, Item 2)
    - Followers of Procrustes, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12, Item 3)
    - Step By Stem From Stem To Stern, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12, Item 4)
    - Evolution viewed in the light of religion, typescript, C. Julian Bartlett, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 12, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - They Also Surf Who Only Stand and Wade, typescript, P. H. Rhinelander, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Who Done It? typescript, Frank Gerbode, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Dealer's Choice, typescript, Willard F. Hamilton, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13, Item 3)
    - Some Roots of Dallas, typescript, Joseph T. Sneed, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 13, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - A Curious Mixture of Geniality and Venom, typescript, Nicholas G. Thacher, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14, Item 1)
    - Trying to Make a Dollar Out of 16 cents, typescript, William R. Reilly, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14, Item 2)
    - From the Tidepool to the Stars, typescript, John E. McCosker, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Introduction by Kevin Starr, typescript, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - 'Tis Not the Drinking that Is to Blame, but the Excess,' or The Story of the First Forty-Niner, typescript, Charles B. Renfrew, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - The Problem of Equality - Serrano Versus Board of Education in 1954, typescript, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Progress, typescript, J. B. deC. M. Saunders, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - The Red Blanket, typescript, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Why? typescript, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Carpe Diem, typescript, circa 1971-1984 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Never More, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - Devil in Deerskins, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Trying to Make a Dollar Out of 16 cents, typescript, William Reilly, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - So long, and thanks for all the fish, typescript, W. Reilly, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Never More, typescript, Ben C. Duniway, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - We'll O'er the Water, We'll O'er the Sea, typescript, Charles Renfrew, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - A Sarga, typescript, John Saunders, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - An Elegant Theory, typescript, Darrell Solom, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - It Ain't Necessarily So, typescript, Frank H. Sloss, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Another Sink? manuscript (photocopy), Henry K. Evers, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - The Second Half, typescript, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - The Principle of Self-Interest Rightly Understood: De Tocqueville Revisited, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Would You Vote for Alcibiades and Talleyrand? typescript, Joseph Sneed, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3, Item 1)
      2 copies.
    - A Needle to the Star, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Austen - Trollope, typescript, William B. Kuder, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - The Purple Land: A Visit to Argentina in April 1986, typescript, T. H. Jukes (Box 13, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - An Uneasy Partnership, typescript, Nick Thatcher, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Heads or Tails or High-Brows, Low-Brows and Egg-Heads, typescript, John Saunders, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Chit Chat Club paper, typescript, William Coblentz, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Mens et Mensa: A Philosophico - Theological Reflection, typescript, Albert Jonsen, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - The Monastic Nutritional Cycle, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - The Sausalito Hum, typescript, John E. McCosker, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 4)
    - IBM and the Thracian Maiden, typescript, Donald Winks, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Food for Thought, typescript, Darrell Salomon, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Does Life Begin at 40? typescript, Theodore L. Eliot, Jr., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - You Have the Right to Remain Silent, typescript, Steven L. Swig, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - The Friendly Arctic, typescript, Thomas Jukes, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Bribery, typescript, John T. Noonan, Jr., 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Antis, typescript, Richmons Crescort, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - The Buonaparte Who Was a Poet, typescript, Joseph T. Sneed, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Prologue, typescript, D. McConnell, circa 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - The World's Oldest Industry, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - How to Watch a Revolution, typescript, Nick Thacher, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Prologue: November 1918, typescript, David Kennedy, 1988? (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Are All Men Created Equal? typescript, Jim Morse, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - The Hidden Hunger, typescript, Thomas [Juhes?], 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - I Think That I Shall Never See, typescript, Steven L. Swig, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - Sharks: Myths and Maneaters, typescript, John E. McCosker, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Murder in Acre, typescript, Mason Willrich, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - What a Difference a Dollar Makes, manuscript (photocopy), W. R. [Reilly?], 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - The Apocalyptical 21st Century, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - The Physician as Essayist, and A San Francisco Institution, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - The George Miller Committee Hearings Sept. 6, 1990, Oakland CA - An Analysis by Thomas H. Jukes, typescript (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Tocsin, typescript, Darrell Salomon, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - 406, 56 and All That, typescript, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 5)
    - The Founder of the Other, typescript, John T. Noonan, Jr., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Nutrition Science from Vitamins to Molecular Biology, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - The Lion by His Claw, typescript, Bruce A. Bolt, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Story Telling: Noting but the Truth? typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - An Auricular Problem or 'What did you say?' typescript, Henry K. Evers, 1990? (Box 14, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Know Then Thyself, typescript, Thomas H. Jukes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - North America on the Fast Track, typescript, Mason Willrich, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - 'One Day Earlier' The Military Risks of Delay: Our Race with Japan for the First Atomic Bomb, typescript, Darrell Salomon, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 3)
    - Pikes Peak or Bust, typescript, John B. Stuppin, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Melting Pot or Salad Bowl, typescript, Theodore L. Eliot, Jr., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - True Confessions? typescript, John T. Noonan, Jr., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Untitled essay, typescript (draft), Doug McConnell, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 3)
    - A Question of Conscience and Ethical Considerations in Relation Thereto, typescript, Ed [Steen?], 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - A Life of Fiber, typescript, Steven L. Swig, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 5)
    - Plain Living and High Thinking, manuscript (photocopy), Bill Reilly, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, n. d. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Chit Chat Club Historic Notes, typescript, Langley Porter, edited by Bill Reilly, n. d. (Box 14, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Strange Story of Santiago de Compostela, typescript, R. Calvert Rutherford, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Agenbite of Inwit, typescript, Thomas H. [Jules?], 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Five Hundred Years of Baja California History, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Hillary, Jackson Hole and the Newly Independent States, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - A Proposal to Provide Universal Health Care in the USA, typescript, Bob Gordon, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Business and Corruption: Framing the Hatian Military Question, typescript, Michel S. Laguerre, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Two Angry Men, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - A Dagger of the Mind, typescript, Darrell Salomon, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 2)
    - The Search for Life, typescript, Thomas Jukes, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - The Children of Promise, typescript, Joseph T. Sneed, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Father Eusebio Francisco Kino: Father of the Californias, typescript, Elmer P. Wheaton, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Bosnia -- Cauldron or Crucible? typescript, William [Schwarzer?], 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The Informal City: The Implosion of Urban America, typescript, Michel S. Laguerre, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - The Supreme Court: Past, Present, and Future, typescript, Sneed, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - The Collecting Phenomenon: A Curious Affliction, typescript, Frank Seidner, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Sugar Plums - [Maj?], typescript, Bill Reilly, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - The Inventors of Romantic Love: The Troubadours of Occitania, typescript, R. Calvert Rutherford, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 2)
    - The Mermaid on the Dolphin's Back, typescript, John Noonan, Jr., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 3)
      3 copies. 1 version printed in The Shakespeare Newsletter, Winter 2001/2002.
    - Nowhere Man, typescript, Steven Otellini, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Smoke and Mirrors, typescript, William W. Schwarzer, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 1)
    - Rivalis, typescript, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 2)
    - Kit-Cat and All That, typescript, Arthur E. Lyons, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Saved By an Earthquake, typescript, R. Calvert Rutherford, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Absurdity and Meaning, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Capitalism, typescript, James R. Morse, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Some Times the Good Guys Wear Black Hats, typescript, John Schram, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - The Pride of Rome: Considerations on the Pantheon, typescript, Steven D. Otellini, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - Whatever Happened to Honor? typescript, Frank Seidner, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - A New Future? typescript, Bill Reilly, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 1)
    - In Search of Equality, typescript, William W. Schwarzer, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 2)
    - God and Caesar - A Recent Confrontation, typescript, Joseph Sneed, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Just Four Blocks Away, typescript, David [Heednut?], 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10, Item 1)
    - Collecting Medical Books, typescript, Arthur Lyons, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10, Item 2)
    - Blind Man's Bluff, typescript, Wade Dickinson, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10, Item 3)
    - Capital Punishment, typescript, Richmond Prescott, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Chit Chat Club essays, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Tragically Difficult, typescript, Buz Thompson, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 1)
    - Election Year 1800, typescript, John Schram, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 2)
    - The Gladstone Club, typescript, John T. Noonan, Jr., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 3)
    - Untitled essay, typescript, Henry Evers, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 4)
    - What Governs History: Man or Fate? typescript, Chark Maser, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 5)
    - Berkeley Center for Globalization and Information Technology, typescript, Michael Laguerre, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11, Item 6)